[Music]
hello everybody it is Nicole from Akili
where I want to help you improve your
art today we'll be reviewing a few
spectrum noir products that were kindly
gifted to me I'll be reviewing the six
piece art liner set and these three sets
of Illustrator markers I'm actually
really excited to try out these markers
because they are brush tip and as you
know most of the markers that I've been
reviewing on my channel have been a
chisel tip and fine tip so I think this
will be a first for brush tip markers so
without further ado let's go ahead and
hop right into that review first I'm
gonna review the markers then I'll move
on to the art liners for the markers
from their website crafters companion
the twelve packs retail for forty four
ninety five and the six pack is
twenty-two ninety-five on Amazon the
twelve packs are around thirty one
dollars if they're on sale if not
they're also 4495 as for the six pack it
is currently priced at sixteen twenty
three overall it seems like the price is
less expensive on Amazon all the links
will be in the description
[Music]
each set comes packaged in thick
cardboard the set name is in the top
left corner along with the swatches of
the colors at the top of the tab it
tells you what tips are on this set the
illustrator sets have a brush and a fine
tip but I do know that their graphic
markers have a chisel and a fine tip on
the back there are swatches of the
colors with their code and names and
there's also a small description in four
languages English French Spanish and
German the markers have a hexagonal
shape to them similar to the Copic
Sketch markers but more angular they are
light gray with the word illustrator
printed on one side it also has an image
of a brush and fine tip printed on it so
you know which side is which there is
also a faint line to indicate the fine
tip side on the top of both caps the
color name and code are shown for the
pros I really enjoyed the brush tip on
this marker I find that I don't actually
use the fine tip as much because the
brush tip can cover both small and large
areas I also have never reviewed another
brush tip marker on this channel before
so this is the first one that I can
really compare 2 kopecks I think that
they are a great alternative to kopecks
because they are also refillable and you
can find them on the website which I'll
link in the description they also have
many more color sets than the ones I've
shown I really like the figure set
because of all these skin tones and
blush tones that they include but I also
enjoy all the pastels in the tint set I
have found that these blend very well
together if you want to see the method I
use to blend markers you can check out
my two tutorial videos on how to color
smoothly with alcohol markers and how to
blend those will be linked in the
description as well as in the eye and
the corner
as for the cons I'm not really sure why
go when applying the marker to the
marker paper it kind of looked like it
was drying out but it wasn't because of
this it takes a little bit more work to
make a smoother blend compared to other
markers overall I really enjoyed these
markers they are less expensive than
kopecks and they are also refillable I
think they are a good alternative to
kopecks or if you want to try out
another marker brand especially if you
enjoy using markers I feel like these
are a great high quality marker to add
to your collection and I'll definitely
be using these and more in the future
now let's move on to the pens for the
six piece art liner set in black on
their website this retails for 16 95 but
when I checked they were out of stock on
Amazon the set is priced at 1159
[Music]
for the packaging it comes in a clear
plastic case and on the inside there is
a piece of plastic to hold the Pens as
well as a thin cardboard with
information on the front and back this
set comes with six pieces five five
liners and one brush pen the pen is all
black with the logo on the side the cap
has a metal clip as well as the nib size
on the pen the brush tip is flexible
whereas the fine tip is really stiff I
did a few tests to see how quickly these
pens dried and to my surprise they
actually dry almost instantly the first
test I did was the smudge test where
after I draw with the pen I run my
finger across it and it didn't actually
smudge at all the next test was using
the marker over the pen to see if it
would smudge and even after applying the
marker within five seconds it actually
didn't smear typically when I use any
fine liner even after it dries and I
apply marker then it would smear somehow
but this one didn't move at all and I
applied several layers of marker
[Music]
for the pros as I mentioned before it
dries extremely quickly
I basically smudged everything or tried
to smudge everything after applying it
and not really waiting or having any
time between so I'm really happy about
that
because typically I don't apply some
fine liners first you will usually see
in my speed paints that I will be
applying marker or paint first and then
applying the fine liner last because
I've had such bad experiences with fine
liner smudging and ruining the drawing
and the next Pro is that it doesn't
smudge under marker which is something
that I've mentioned before about how my
bad experiences will fineliners keep it
reoccurring as for the cons although the
package says these pens are black I
think they are definitely more gray than
black definitely lighter than a really
deep black so if you want something
that's super dark I probably wouldn't
suggest these ones as your black go to
fine liner overall if you want a pen
that dries extremely quickly and doesn't
smudge under marker then I would highly
suggest these however if you want
something that's a deeper black then I
would probably go for a different brand
I hope you found this review useful or
helpful in any way if you're interested
in seeing more reviews like this be sure
to subscribe and hit that notification
belt so you're notified of when new
videos come out and if you enjoyed this
video please give this video a thumbs up
and leave a comment down below telling
me if you might get these markers or if
there's any other things you want me to
review so with that I want to thank you
guys so much for joining me today
keep drawing keep creating and I'll see
you guys next time bye
[Music]
you